©
© P @ rM ! NdeR
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ ™
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ ™ Mobile - + 919815899536
Take a sample of her blood
and then get rid of that . - Yes , sir .
The Umbrella Corporation thought they 'd contained the infection .
Well , they were wrong .
Raccoon City was just the beginning .
Within weeks , the T-virus had consumed the United States .
Within months , the world .
The virus didn 't just wipe out human life .
Lakes and rivers dried up , forests became deserts
and whole continents were reduced to
nothing more than barren wastelands .
Slowly but surely , the Earth began to wither and die .
What few survivors there were learned to keep on the move .
We avoided major cities .
If we stopped anyplace too long , they would be drawn to us .
Only a few at first , but then more and more .
A never-ending army of undead .
For those of us left
staying on the road
seemed the only way to stay alive .
This is KLKB .
We have seven people here
in need of urgent medical attention .
We need help .
This is KLKB .
Can anyone hear us ?
Can anyone help us ? Please ?
My baby .
Please .
Please help my baby .
You bitch .
You dropped my baby .
" We 're surrounded . We need help .
Can anyone hear us ?
- Can anyone help us ? Please . "
- Works every time , Mama .
Let 's see
what else she 's packing . - Yeah .
What you got down there , fishy ?
I wouldn 't do that .
Shut your mouth !
- Relax ! - Just show the bitch .
Eddie ! Eddie ! Eddie !
Jesus Christ ! He 's dead !
Think you 're pretty smart , huh ?
Well , you 'll see .
There you go , bitch .
I wouldn 't want it to be over too fast !
Open the cage !
Let them loose .
Get up now !
That was a juicy one , huh ?
Hey , Carlos , this is Claire .
- You got any smokes ? - No .
Like I 'm supposed to believe that .
Claire , would I lie to you ?
- L.J. - Claire Redfield , how can I help you ?
Got any smokes ?
No can do .
How about alternate ?
Sorry to say we 're out of that too .
You gotta be shitting me . Otto ?
Sorry , campers .
Smoked the last of it back in Salt Lake .
Damn .
- Yeah , people ... - Damn it .
... it really is the end of the world .
- Anyone else ? - Paris facility .
Food supplies down to 50 percent .
Six casualties .
Biohazard numbers increasing .
London facility .
Food supplies down to 28 percent .
Seventeen casualties .
Biohazard numbers increasing .
Gentlemen .
Dr. Isaacs .
How good of the science division to join us .
Chairman Wesker . I 've been busy .
On the subject of the biohazard , what is the science division 's report ?
Well , we now know conclusively that they have no real need for sustenance .
They hunger for flesh but do not require it .
My research indicates they could remain active for decades .
We 're to be trapped underground for decades ?
What news of Project Alice ?
Using antibodies from her blood
I will develop a serum that will not just combat the effects of the T-virus
but potentially reverse it
giving back these creatures a measure of their intelligence
their memories , thus curbing their hunger for flesh .
You 're confident you can domesticate them ?
They 're animals , essentially .
We can train them , if we can take away their baser instincts .
They 'll never be human
but would provide the basis for a docile workforce .
We can return to the surface .
After months of experiments , you have nothing to show .
We are left to rot underground .
Without the original Project Alice
progress has been difficult .
I 've been forced to replicate her using cloned genetic models .
It 's laborious .
The results , unpredictable .
Project Alice and the subject of domestication is of the highest priority .
You will concentrate on this to the exclusion of all other research .
We expect an updated report in a week .
Simply demanding results will not guarantee them .
Then perhaps we should place someone else in charge .
Someone who can give us the reassurances we require .
Continue with your research , doctor
while it still is your research .
This meeting is adjourned .
Sorry about this , Stevie .
This is Claire Redfield 's convoy , broadcasting for any survivors .
Is anybody out there ?
Broadcasting for any survivors .
This is Claire Redfield 's convoy , broadcasting for any survivors .
Is anybody out there ?
This is Claire Redfield 's convoy .
Location , the Desert Trail Motel .
Broadcasting for any survivors .
Is there anybody in there ?
Keep trying , Mikey .
Is there anyone alive in there ?
Please respond .
Seems quiet .
Yeah , don 't they always ?
Is there anyone alive in there ?
Please respond .
Claire . Looks clear .
Shall we go in ?
It 's your call , boys .
Come on .
Let 's go .
Let 's do it .
I 'm gonna get me a room .
I 'll take a waterbed , a Jacuzzi
and I 'm gonna rent me a porno .
What happened ? You two okay ?
Yeah . It 's all clear .
Somebody need my help ?
It 's nothing .
But if you insist ...
That 's right .
So sit back and relax .
Spread out .
Look for anything of use .
Gas , food , ammo .
You know the drill .
You like playing rough , huh ?
- Oh , I 've had worse . - I 'm sure .
But you 've always been gentle with me , Betty .
Oh , God .
I 'm leaving .
So , what do we say , dinner at my place tonight ?
Oh , I 'm there .
Hey , Betty !
Over here !
This is amazing .
He knows what it is .
Camera .
You try .
Stand your ground .
- My God . - Unbelievable .
He has memory and reasoning skills .
This is incredible .
The serum works .
You 've domesticated them .
You 've done it .
Congratulations .
No , doctor ! Please . No !
No , no , doctor . Please , no !
Pork and beans .
I 'll get some peaches for the little one there .
There you go .
- It 's asparagus . - Thanks .
For you
cat food .
Just kidding . It 's pork and beans .
- Hey . - What 's this , huh ?
- Soup . Cream of mushroom . - Bullshit .
I think that 's pork and beans too .
Thanks , man .
- I 'll be damned . - Asparagus .
How do you do that ?
Just one of my skills .
It 's a dying art , unfortunately .
This is the last of it .
I think it 's some kind of fruit .
Thanks , Otto .
Sorry , that 's all we have .
Fruit . You want some fruit ?
Did you check out the gas station ?
Yep , it 's bone-dry .
Well , how we looking here ?
Well , Claire , if we can run these trucks on rust
we 're looking pretty good .
All right .
Hey , sweetheart .
Perimeter up yet ?
It 's almost done .
- Who 's out there ? - Olivera .
- Hey , Carlos . - Claire .
All that smoking is slowing you down .
Get your ass in gear , old man .
I want my perimeter up .
Last sentinel in place .
Perimeter 's up and running .
All motion sensors online .
Cameras 100 percent .
Refried beans .
Fruit salad .
Oh , my favorite .
Storm 's coming !
Let 's start packing it up and move it inside .
- Come on , kids , let 's go ! - Hurry up !
Get back in the bus .
Put this fire out .
©
© P @ rM ! NdeR
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ
This is Claire Redfield 's convoy .
Location , the Desert Trail Motel .
Lat . 35 , long . 114 .
Calling any survivors .
This is Claire Redfield 's convoy .
Location , the Desert Trail Motel .
Lat . 35 , long . 114 .
Calling any survivors .
Activate Number 87 .
Shit .
- Dr. Isaacs . - What is it ?
My sensors have detected a peak in psionic activity .
Both alpha and beta wave .
From Number 87 ?
No , the activity 's not from one of the clones .
It occurred outside the complex .
That 's not possible .
My sensors were quite clear .
Massive psionic activity was detected 15 minutes ago
centered on a desert location .
- Claire ! - What ?
What the hell ?
Oh , God .
- Carlos . - I see them .
Everybody stay in your trucks .
What 's going on ?
Everyone just stay in your trucks .
Roll up the windows and keep quiet .
Okay , close the windows up .
What 's wrong with their eyes ?
They 've been feeding on infected flesh .
Fire it up .
Let 's get out of here .
That 's a hell of an idea .
Lock and load .
We 're stuck !
Hell , no , let 's get out of here .
Let 's head for the bus , come on .
Come on ! Go ! Go !
Come on , get in !
Come on , come on , come on .
Claire !
Damn it .
Mikey , Carlos , we have to evac the bus .
You got it .
Hold it !
Come on , move !
Keep moving !
Come on ! Go ! Go !
Go ! Come on !
- Betty ! - Go ! Just go !
Get out of here , Betty ! Go !
- Move ! Move ! Move ! - Go !
- Betty ! Betty ! - L.J. , hurry up !
Come with me !
Come on !
Come on ! Betty ! Betty !
No !
Betty !
Go ! Go ! Go !
Dr. Isaacs .
Another spike in alpha and beta waves detected .
Forty-five percent probability that this is Project Alice .
Triangulate . Find her location .
Impressive .
If it is her , her development is extraordinary .
Her powers would appear to have grown at a geometric rate
since her escape from the Detroit facility .
You 've made 10 trips to the surface in the past 24 hours .
All unauthorized .
Any trip to the surface , especially to gather specimens , puts my men at risk .
Why do you need so many all of a sudden ?
Isaacs !
My research has intensified .
Don 't worry .
They 're perfectly secure .
You 're supposed to be domesticating them .
Sometimes aggression has its uses .
What could you possibly need these things for ?
Dr. Isaacs .
Specimen 87 has reached the final stage of the test grid .
Perfect . Put her on the screen .
Good girl .
Is Chairman Wesker even aware of this ?
He knows what he needs to know .
You 've overstepped your mark .
My research will change the face of everything .
If you pick a side
be sure it 's the right one .
Hi .
Hey .
This belong to you ?
I gave it to you last night .
For luck .
Thank you .
What 's your name ?
K-Mart .
It 's where they found me .
Claire and the other ...
A few years back .
Do you have another name ?
Never liked it .
Everyone I knew was dead
so seemed like time for a change .
Anyone want to say something ?
Alice , this is Claire Redfield .
She 's the one who put this convoy together .
Thank you so much for your help .
Claire !
Excuse me . I have things I have to attend to .
In the last six months , she lost half of the convoy .
Pretty soon there 'll be more of us dead than alive .
Alice , what happened to you ?
Why did you leave after Detroit ?
I didn 't have a choice .
They were using me .
What do you mean ?
They were tracking me .
I couldn 't be around you .
Any of you .
I would 've gotten you all killed .
That 's why you disappeared ?
Broke into an Umbrella facility and hacked into their computers
downloaded the satellite trajectories
and stayed off the grid .
And after the world ended ?
Why stay out there alone ?
It 's just safer if I 'm not around people .
Why 'd you come back ?
Damn !
What time is it ?
Chase , what time is it ?
Well , Carlos , it is 12 : 14 . Why ?
You got somewhere you gotta be ?
Guess I 'm just being paranoid .
Welcome home .
Got a minute ?
Yeah .
Everyone is grateful for you helping us out .
But how long am I gonna stay ?
Don 't get me wrong .
We really are grateful .
They 're all talking about what you did .
And they 're scared .
I don 't blame them .
People have a habit of dying around me .
Not just you .
You 're positive it 's her ?
Sixty-two percent .
Too great a chance to pass up .
If it is Project Alice , she 's been evading the satellite grid for years .
I 've re-routed the remaining satellites .
We can reacquire the subject .
She 'll be unaware of surveillance .
I can have a strike team ready within the hour .
No . We 'll establish a positive identification first .
One hundred percent .
The group she 's with include known associates .
The original Project Alice is vital to my research
to the whole process of domestication . Her blood
her genetic structure , is the key .
The longer she 's out there , the greater chance we lose her .
I can 't risk that .
That decision isn 't yours to make .
Take no action until this matter has been discussed by the committee
at the next scheduled meeting .
And , doctor
that 's an order .
These transmissions are the best indication of life we 've seen in months .
- Alaska ? - We have to check it out .
We can 't just ignore it .
Any idea what kind of journey that would be ?
Yeah . A long one .
And at the end of it , what ?
You have no guarantee there 's even anyone alive up there .
These transmissions say that ...
They 're dated six months ago .
How many radio broadcasts have we responded to ?
How many times have we got there too late ?
The transmissions say that there 's no infection up there .
It 's isolated .
Safe .
This convoy trusts me with their lives .
These people don 't need pipe dreams .
Maybe that 's exactly what they need .
Look at them , Claire .
Six months ago , there were 50 of us , then 40 , now there 's less than 30 .
They 're starting to give up .
They need some kind of hope .
We have a decision to make .
And it 's too big , it 's too important for me to make for you .
There 's a chance there are survivors .
Where ?
In Alaska .
There is a chance
that the infection hasn 't reached that far .
But we don 't know for sure .
So we have a choice .
We stay as we are
or we try for Alaska .
For Alaska .
Alaska .
I hope you 're right .
God .
The food 's virtually gone and the truck 's running on empty .
I 've got half a tank of gas .
That 's it .
- Chase ? - Shit , I don 't even have empty .
I got enough for a hundred miles , tops .
If we 're gonna make this trip , we 'll need to resupply .
Yep .
These are our options .
The nearest , safest bet is right there .
No , it 's empty . I tried that .
Then , well , maybe ...
- We could try this ... - Vegas .
It 's the only place we 're sure to find gas and supplies .
There 's a reason for that .
Vegas is too dangerous .
It 's crawling with them sons of bitches .
We 've drained every small town dry over the last six months .
We have to hit a big city .
She 's right .
Vegas , it 's our only bet .
We 'll establish a positive identification .
One hundred percent .
Take no action until this matter has been discussed by the committee .
Doctor
that 's an order .
The committee authorizes immediate action .
Release of vehicles and personnel
under command of Dr. Isaacs .
That 's an order .
Hey . You all right ?
Yeah , I 'm fine .
Them pork and beans , they lethal .
I don 't see how you cowboys do it .
Years of practice .
Oh , my God .
What happened to it ?
The desert must have taken it back .
Five years .
No one to keep the sand back .
It 's empty .
No undead .
Nothing .
Those birds must have moved through the city block by block .
Picked it clean .
I don 't see any truck stops .
Where are they ?
There .
Valet parking at the casino up ahead .
There 's gas pumps in there .
Now , how do you know that ?
I dropped two G 's back in the day here .
You lost $ 2000 ?
Damn it .
Spread them out !
We 're gonna have to move it .
All right , Chase , I need a lookout !
Up there .
Great .
Climb the Eiffel Tower with a high-powered rifle .
A few years ago , that would 've caused a stir .
Well , let the good times roll .
Let 's get this done .
Get the hell out of here .
Mikey , get the winch .
- Yeah . - Carlos .
Wait .
Get back !
- Carlos , cover me ! - Go !
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ ™
Move !
Just get to the back and stay quiet .
Go ! Now ! Go !
Get down !
She really is magnificent .
When she 's dead , make sure you move in fast .
I need a sample of her blood while it 's still warm .
That won 't be a problem .
- Satellite in position ? - Yes , sir .
Then shut her down .
Mikey !
Hey !
No !
She 's fighting the conditioning .
Boost the control signal .
Shit !
Climb ! Give me your hand !
Run ! Go !
Go ! Run !
Let 's go !
L.J. !
L.J.
What is it ?
Satellite . Some kind of malfunction .
How long ?
New feed coming online in 15 seconds .
Online in three , two ...
Now .
Where the hell is she going ?
Shut her down !
She 's still coming !
- Now ! - Oh , shit .
You son of a ...
Back to base !
The anti-virus !
Get me the anti-virus !
Why didn 't you shoot ?
Because we 're not driving to Alaska .
I want that helicopter intact .
Let 's go look at the computer , see where that chopper 's headed .
- How is he ? - Under house arrest
as you instructed .
He 's been quiet .
How much of this have you used ?
Her blood increased the creatures ' power .
It also increased the strength of the infection .
I needed it .
You have no idea what this will do to you .
Oh , I have an idea .
You 're out of control .
Well , this ends here .
Under executive order 1345 , issued by Chairman Wesker
for gross misconduct in the field
I sentence you to summary liquidation .
Liquidation ?
Just die .
Take the body to the surface .
Bring me the stats on Program Alice ...
Sir !
Good thing we like a challenge .
Hold on .
They have the anti-virus in there .
Just hold on .
It 's too late , and you know it .
Besides , you need a way to get in there .
And I have an idea .
- You keep them safe , huh ? - You got it .
Come here .
Carlos , I ...
Save it .
You just promise me one thing .
When you get down there ...
Consider it done .
Wish I had a smoke .
Fuck !
I 'll be damned .
L.J. , you sneaky son of a bitch .
Oh , hell .
Come on .
Get the kids out quickly !
Go !
- Run ! Run ! Hurry up ! - Okay .
Go ! Go ! Go !
Take him !
You 're not coming ?
Take care of the others .
I 'm sorry .
I didn 't mean to startle you .
I am the artificial intelligence ...
I know what you are .
I knew your sister .
She was a homicidal bitch .
My sister computer was merely following the most logical path
for the preservation of human life .
Yeah . Kill a few , save a lot .
So , what happened here ?
Dr. Isaacs returned in an infected state .
He was bitten by a creature
that had been treated with a newly developed serum .
A serum derived from your blood .
The resulting infection has caused massive mutation .
My blood ?
Your blood has bonded with the T-virus .
Dr. Isaacs correctly deduced
that it could be used to destroy the biohazard for good .
You mean my blood is the cure for all this ?
Correct .
So why are you helping me ?
Your blood is pure , and this facility contains
all of the equipment you will require to synthesize a cure .
- You mean this could all end ? - Correct .
There is , however
a small problem .
I have him contained in the lower levels
but I cannot hold him there for much longer .
All right , let 's go .
Alice ?
Good luck .
©
© P @ rM ! NdeR
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ
You can 't kill me .
I 've told you
I can 't die .
No .
For so long , I thought you were the future .
I was wrong .
I am the future .
No .
You 're just
another asshole .
And we 're both gonna die down here .
Yeah , you 're the future , all right .
All attempts to contact the North American facility continue to fail .
How long have they been off the air ?
Seventeen hours .
We must consider them lost .
But our plans remain unchanged .
All data will be transferred to this facility
and the research will continue under my personal supervision .
I expect results within one month .
You won 't have to wait that long , boys .
Because I 'm coming for you .
And
I 'm gonna be bringing a few of my friends .
You 're just
another asshole .
©
© P @ rM ! NdeR
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ